<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalProject</string>
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="oppo_reno_7">OPPO RENO 7</string>

    <string name="oppo_reno_7_z_5g">OPPO RENO 7 Z 5G</string>
    <string name="vivo_Y12" />
    <string name="vivo_y12">VIVO Y12</string>
    <string name="vivo_v20">VIVO V20</string>
    <string name="ASUS_ZENFONE">ASUS ZENFONE</string>
    <string name="title_activity_opporeno7">opporeno7</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <!--    kategori laptop - acer - acer spin 3-->
    <string name="tittleAcersplin3"><b>Thin, Light, and Versatile</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nWhether you’re using the screen to
        read, take notes, sketch, or share your work –it rotates with complete ease. When urgency
        strikes, quickly modify the backlight (3 levels), caps lock, and speakers with a push of a button.
        </font>
        \n\n<b>Drawing and Writing on the Go</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nYou’re going to want a laptop with a stylus to stay ready on the go. The dockable Acer
        Active Stylus with Wacom AES 1.01,2 can be docked to recharge the stylus in just 15 seconds
        for 90 minutes of unfettered use.
        </font>

    </string>

    <string name="deskAcerSplin3"><b>Processor</b> <font color="#878787">Intel Core i5 (8th Gen) Processor</font>
        \n<b>RAM</b> <font color="#878787">8 GB DDR4 RAM</font>
        \n<b>Storage</b> <font color="#878787">1 TB HDD</font>
        \n<b>Display</b> <font color="#878787">14" (35.56 cm) display, 1920 x 1080px</font></string>


    <!--    kategori laptop - acer - acer spin 5-->
    <string name="tittleAcersplin5"><b>TBrilliant 14” Touchscreen Display</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nWhether you’re using the screen to read, take notes, sketch,
            or share your work – it rotates with complete ease and feels easy on the eyes thanks
            to the low-blue-light TÜV Certified2 display.
        </font>
        \n\n<b>Ready for Any Task</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nBuilt on the Intel® Evo™ platform for high standards in performance
            and battery life. Intel processors and graphics accelerate your productivity and editing
            needs, giving you confidence for those everyday tasks.
        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="deskAcerSplin5"><b>Processor</b> <font color="#878787">Intel Core i7-8550U (8th Gen)</font>
        \n<b>RAM</b> <font color="#878787">	8 GB</font>
        \n<b>Storage</b> <font color="#878787">512 GB SSD</font>
        \n<b>Display</b> <font color="#878787">13.3 Inches</font>
    </string>


    <!--    kategori laptop - asus - asus zenbook 13 flip-->
    <string name="tittleAsusz13flip"><b>Maximum display precision</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nSeniman, fotografer, dan desainer akan menyukai apa yang ditawarkan
            oleh tampilan NanoEdge yang dikombinasikan dengan ASUS Pen yang tersedia terpisah. Layar
            sentuh sehalus sutra mendukung 4096 tingkat sensitivitas tekanan yang ditawarkan ASUS
            Pen, memberikan pengalaman yang ditingkatkan yang menjadikan ZenBook Flip 13 pilihan
            sempurna Anda untuk kreativitas kasual, membuat catatan, dan mengedit secara intuitif
            di aplikasi yang didukung.
        </font>
        \n\n<b>Extreme battery life</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nZenBook Flip 13 hadir dengan baterai berkapasitas tinggi yang
            tidak akan mengecewakan Anda, betapapun lama dan beratnya hari kerja Anda. Teknologi
            fast-charging memungkinkan Anda mengisi ulang hingga 60% kapasitas hanya dalam 49
            menit, sehingga Anda dapat aktif dan bekerja lebih cepat dari sebelumnya. ASUS USB-C
            Easy Charge memungkinkan Anda menggunakan berbagai pengisi daya USB-C standar untuk
            pengisian daya yang nyaman saat bepergian.
        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="deskAsusz13flip"><b>Processor</b> <font color="#878787">Intel Core i7 (8th Gen) Processor</font>
        \n<b>RAM</b> <font color="#878787">	Intel Core i7 (8th Gen) Processor</font>
        \n<b>Storage</b> <font color="#878787">	512 GB SSD</font>
        \n<b>Display</b> <font color="#878787">	13.3" (33.78 cm) display, 1920 x 1080 px</font>
    </string>


    <!--    kategori laptop - asus - asus zenbook 14 flip-->
    <string name="tittleAsusz14flip"><b>Unbounded beauty</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nSDirancang untuk memberi Anda lebih banyak area layar dalam ruang
            fisik yang lebih kecil, desain NanoEdge memiliki bezel yang lebih ramping di keempat
            sisinya untuk membuat visual yang lebih mendalam, dengan sedikit gangguan untuk mata
            Anda. Dilengkapi dengan fitur teknologi WideView untuk gambar yang jelas bahkan ketika
            dilihat dari sudut ekstrim. ZenBook 14 memiliki tampilan yang tajam, jernih, resolusi
            tinggi yang membuat visual apa pun terlihat terbaik, dengan sudut pandang lebar dan
            warna yang jelas dan akurat.
        </font>
        \n\n<b>Extraordinary elegance</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nNamun, tak satu pun dari gaya ZenBook tradisional yang hilang:
            ada patern lingkaran logam ikonik yang terinspirasi dari Zen pada penutupnya dan
            pilihan Royal Blue yang prestisius atau sentuhan akhir Icicle Silver yang canggih,
            keduanya baru ditingkatkan dengan panel trim Rose Gold yang kontras di atas keyboard
            untuk sentuhan ekstra mewah. Warna Royal Blue yang elegan terinspirasi oleh keindahan
            matahari terbit keemasan yang menakjubkan di atas samudra biru tua. Icicle Silver yang
            canggih mencerminkan kontras yang menakjubkan antara emas asli dan perak bulan,
            pasangan serasi yang dirayakan dalam tema klasik ini.
        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="deskAsusz14flip"><b>Processor</b> <font color="#878787"> Intel Core i7-10510U (10th Gen)</font>
        \n<b>RAM</b> <font color="#878787">	16 GB</font>
        \n<b>Storage</b> <font color="#878787">	512 GB SSD</font>
        \n<b>Display</b> <font color="#878787">	14 Inches (35.56 cm)x</font>
    </string>

    <!--    kategori laptop - lenovo - legion 5i-->
    <string name="tittleLenovolegion5i"><b>Streamlined power</b>
        <font color="#878787">\nMenawarkan berbagai pilihan kinerja untuk semua level gamers,
            Legion 5i memadukan fleksibilitas dengan kekuatan luar biasa, serta desain yang
            stylish dan minimalis. Didukung oleh hingga 10th Gen Intel®Core™i7 H processors,
            optional NVIDIA®GeForce GTX™graphics, dan banyak memori, tidak hanya Anda dapat
            memainkan game AAA favorit Anda, tetapi mereka akan hidup kembali di layar Anda.
        </font>
        \n\n<b>Advanced Coldfront Cooling </b>
        <font color="#878787">\nLegion 5i tetap tenang, sekeras apa pun Anda mendorongnya dengan
            sistem Coldfront 2.0 yang mendinginkan dan menghilangkan panas melalui mekanisme
            termal dua saluran dari 67 bilah kipas yang dilapisi polimer kristal cair dan pipa
            tembaga. Ini artinya laptop Anda akan berjalan optimal, sehingga Anda selalu bisa
            berada di puncak permainan Anda. Dan dengan Q Control 3.0 yang memungkinkan Anda untuk
            memilih antara mode termal Quiet, Balance, dan Performance secara manual, Anda akan
            serta merta berubah dari NOOBS menjadi seperti PRO. Juga, setiap laptop Legion memiliki
            Dual Burn Support, mendorong CPU; GPU bersama untuk kinerja maksimal dalam game.
        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="deskLenovolegion5i"><b>Processor</b> <font color="#878787"> Intel Core i7 11th Gen Core i7-11400H</font>
        \n<b>RAM</b> <font color="#878787">	8 GB</font>
        \n<b>Storage</b> <font color="#878787">	256GB</font>
        \n<b>Display</b> <font color="#878787">	16 Inches</font>
    </string>


    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    ASUS ZENFONE 5S

</resources>
